Abderraouf MADANI

Owner and Full-stack developer at AYL GROUP

https://raouf-cv.com | https://ayoungleader.com



https://github.com/raouf-madani/

OBJECTIVE

Senior Web & Mobile Developer specializing in front-end and backend development and I recently founded my Startup AYL. My team and I developed the first product which is a booking mobile app of haircut and beauty services in Algeria. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript ES6, JQuery, NodeJS, Express, PHP, MySQL, React, ReactNative, Redux and Wordpress. Strong background in Leadership, Project management, public speaking and customer relations.

SKILLS

Javascript ES6 (85%) React Native (95%) Reactjs(70%) 2 EJS (65%) NodeJS (70%) Redux (90%) 2 HTML5(85%) CSS3 (95%) 2 Bootstrap (85%) JQuery (75%) 2 Ajax (75%) 2 MySQL (85%) 2 MongoDB (65%) 2 PostgreSQL (60%) 2 PHP (80%) 2 PYTHON (65%) 2 WEB HOSTING (90%) 2 Linux Virtual Private Server(90%) 2 WORDPRESS (90%) 2 WOOCOMMERCE (95%) 2 Web Content (80%) Digital Marketing (50%) O.AUTH 2.0(85%) MAC OS(90%) Technical Support (90%) Leadership (98%) 2 Solution Oriented (90%) 2 Self-Confidence (100%) 2 Team Management (80%) 2 Project Management (80%) 2 Presentation Skills (90%) Public Speaking (90%) World Citizen (85%) Work Ethics (95%)

Arabic English French

EDUCATION and CERTIFICATIONS

09/2014 to 06/2017 Bachelor in Computer Science System

SAAD DAHLAB UNIVERSITY (USDB)

08/03/2021 to The Online Professional English Network Orientation Course
02/04/2021 Sponsored by the U.S Department of State with funding provided by
the U.S GOVERNMENT and administered by FHI 360

07/2015 to 05/2020 1-The Complete 2020 Web Development Bootcamp

2- ReactNative Mobile Apps, The Complete React Native + Hooks Course [2020

3- Complete Online Training Web Developer

4- The Complete JavaScript Course 2019: Build Real Projects! *Udemy By Jonas Schmetmann, Angela Yu, Maximilian Schwarzmuller and Jhon Taieb*

INTERNATIONAL VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCES & INTERNSHIPS

18/11/2019 - 30/12/2019 Izmir, TURKEY

Ege Test Center

Full Stack developer

- Design database architecture.
- Front-end + back-end.
- PHP|JAVASCRIPT|CHILD THEME|DIVI|WORDPRESS|HTML5|CSS3|WOOCOMMERCE
- <u>CertifyMyProduct</u> Ecommerce Website

05/10/2019 - 15/11/2019

DVLX COMPANY

Izmir, TURKEY

Full Stack developer

- Design database architecture.
- Front-end + back-end.
- WORDPRESS | HTML5 | CSS3 | PHP | WOOCOMMERCE
- Mobilmed Ecommerce Website.
- Collaboration with Mr. Armagan ERGUN

10/09/2018 - 19/10/2018

Volunteer experience at primary schools of Warsaw

Warsaw, POLAND

Culture teacher

- Certificates of Attendance in International education project in Warsaw and Cisie.
- Certificate of leadership.
- Powered by AIESEC Warsaw.

08/07/2017- 20/08/2017 Craiova, ROMANIA

Volunteer experience at kindergartens of Craiova city

Culture teacher

- Certificate of leadership
- Powered by Aiesec

COMPETITIONS

02/01/2020 - 19/12/2020 Algiers, ALGERIA

Algeria Startup Challenge 2020

Co-Founder and mobile developer of ReBorn

- Winner of the first price among 700 projects
- Our final presentation (Youtube Video)
- ReBorn, a booking mobile App of haircut and beauty services for men and women.
- Powered by Algérie Poste, UNDP, OOREDOO, SANOFI, SATIM, YASSIR...

17/03/2020 - 17/08/2020

Algiers, ALGERIA

CORONHACKATHON

Co-Founder and mobile developer of ReBorn

- Laureate project.
- Our presentation video's link and event's link.
- ReBorn, a booking mobile App of haircut and beauty services for men and women.
- Powered by United Nations Development Programme (UNDP)

24/12/2020 – 26/12/2020 INTERNATIONAL HACKATHON JUNCTION X (Online)

Mobile developer

woone developer

Runner up project.

- Event's link
- Information management using Tech assets by BMS Electric.

24/12/2020 - 26/12/2020 Algiers, ALGERIA

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE and REASERCHES

01/05/2021 - Now

Algiers, ALGERIA

01/04/2021 - 31/04/2021

Nijmegen, NETHERLANDS

16/11/2020 - 30/03/2021

Blida, ALGERIA

02/01/2020 - 19/12/2020

Algiers, ALGERIA

AYL GROUP LLC

Owner and Full Stack developer

- Incorporate a private limited IT company.
- Business and administration

Schade24 version 2

Project chef

- Managing the team from the website architecture to the front end part.
- Fixing bugs using Github and web development tolos.
- HTML/CSS, Jquery and Bootstrap.
- Figma Link, Front-end link.
- Attending Whatsapp meetings with the owner.
- Remote Job

Blida University 1 (USDB)

Project chef, Full-stack developer and trainer

- Coordinated more than 20 meetings with the University Staff.
- Website architecture + frontend + backend (Co-working)
- Trained the website administrators and faculties deleguates (18 sessions)
- University's website
- Final video presentation.

Mobile booking app of haircut and beauty services

Mobile developer and Co-founder

- Cooperate with a designer and a mobile developerto create clean interfaces, intuitive interactions and experiences.
- Design project's database and maintain optimal workflow.
- Complete detailed programming and development tasks for front-end as well as back-end server code.
- Carry out quality assurance tests to discover errors and optimize usability.
- Technologies: React native, JS ES6, Redux, NodeJS, Express, MySQL, Firebase Authentification
 Service
- Planning future activities of the project and representing the team at media (TV, video capsule, radio...)
- ReBorn app link and Reborn partner app's link

03/08/2020 - 31/08/2020 BEZWAAR 24

Nijmegen, NETHERLANDS

Full-Stack developer

- Front-end development (JQuery, JS, Bootstrap, HTML/CSS)
- Back-end development (Integrate Wordpress dashboard using PHP)
- Home page, blog page and post page.
- Bezwaar24 website
- Remote Job

01/07/2020 - 31/07/2020

Nijmigen, ALGERIA

SCHADE24 version 1

Backend developer

- Cooperate with a full-stack developer
- Remote Job
- Back-end: Integration of schade24 into Wordpress from SCRATCH using PHP
- Schade 24 version 1 website

24/12/2020 - 26/12/2020

Medea, ALGERIA

DX SOLUTIONS

Chef project and full-stack developer

- Cooperate with a full-stack developer
- Remote Job
- Lead all appointments with customers and Communication skills and customer relations.
- E-learning platform of the Paramedical Institute of Chlef city
- E-learning platform of Private Paramedical School ofOran city, El Bibane
- E-learning platform of the Higher Paramedical Instituteof Mostaganem city
- Web languages used for this project: PHP7, HTML5/CSS3& JAVASCRIPT ES5
- CMS used for this project: WORDPRESS, WPLMS CHILD THEME
- WordPress Hooks used for this project: Actions & Filters

18/11/2019 - 31/12/2019

Izmir, TURKEY

TESTUPS

Full Stack developer

- Solving security threat of malicious or unwanted malware Adwords
- Hosting services issues (DNS, NameServers, SMTP..)
- CertifyMyProduct Ecommerce Website
- Web languages used for this project: PHP7, HTML5/CSS3& JAVASCRIPT ES5
- CMS used for this project: WORDPRESS, DIVI CHILDTHEME & WOOCOMMERCE
- Technical Support Request (Godaddy, Bluehost and Google) | French & English

05/10/2019 - 15/11/2019

Izmir, TURKEY

DVLX COMPANY

Full Stack developer

- Full-Stack developer at Ege Test Center Company
- Solving security threat of malicious or unwanted malware Adwords
- Hosting services issues (DNS, NameServers, SMTP..)
- CertifyMyProduct Ecommerce Website
- Web languages used for this project: PHP7, HTML5/CSS3& JAVASCRIPT ES5
- CMS used for this project: WORDPRESS, DIVI CHILDTHEME & WOOCOMMERCE
- Technical Support Request (Godaddy, Bluehost and Google) | French & English

05/08/2019 - 05/09/2019

Algiers, ALGERIA

SHIFT'IN AGENCY

Back end developer

- Shiftin's Blog and Github Link
- Back-end: Integration of bezwaar24 web pagesinto Wordpress from SCRATCH using PHP
- Web languages used for this project: PHP, HTML/CSS& JAVASCRIPT
- Responsivity techniques used for this project: MEDIA QUERIES

26/06/2018 - 26/08/2018

Algiers, ALGERIA

CELERSHIP

Full Stack developer

- Creating and designing dynamic websites with Wordpress/CSS3/HTML5
- 1- Ecommerce websites : ALS 2018
- Dynamic and Static websites : Sauce Haines (Expired)
- Polyglot 2018
- Auxilium 2018
- Swalis 2018
- Fond Du Coeur 2018

05/08/2019 to 05/09/2019

Blida and Algiers, ALGERIA

KERKECH SYSTEM, CLEVERTECH and iSCHOOLGENIUS

Senior trainer

- February 2017 at Kerkech System WordPress : Create a Beautiful Dynamic Website
- 16/02/2018 to 24/02/2018 at Clever Tech Startup Introduction to Web Development and LearnWordPress
- 04/04/2018 to 07/04/2018 at Clever Tech Startup 2nd Edition of Introduction to Web Development and Learn WordPress Create a Beautiful Dynamic Website
- 23/12/2018 to 26/12/2018 at Clever Tech Startup 3rd Edition of Introduction to Web Development and Learn WordPress Create a Beautiful Dynamic Website
- 30/06/2019 to 04/07/2019 at iSchoolGenius Build your website with WordPress + Intro to E-commerce